{
    "id": "226e43d5fcb7478985aef69c979d3d04",
    "title": "Match up (adverbs of time)",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "c47372c781be4f21b4fdd759364637e1",
            "title": "Adverbs Of Time",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I have known her ................................ a long time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "since",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I once studied the guitar ................................ three years.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "since",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have been working .................................. six o’clock, and I am getting tired.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "for",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It was the worst storm ............................... ten years.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "from",
                        "since"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will be here .................................. three o’clock onwards.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "from",
                        "for",
                        "since"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": ".................................... now on, I’m going to go running every day.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "From",
                        "Since",
                        "For"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "....................................... the dawn of civilization, people have made war.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "From",
                        "In",
                        "For"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "By next Christmas, we will have been here ................................. eight years.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "for",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I think the plane is ..................................... to take off.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "about",
                        "around"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The President is to visit Beijing .............................. May.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "on",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}